Finding aid for the Getty Education Institute for the Arts, Grant Files, 1984-2001 IA10021
Institutional Records and Archives
- Regional Institute grants, 1986-2001; II.; 61 Linear Feet (64 boxes)
  - Regional Grants Administration
    - Regional Institute Meetings:
      - Directors' Meeting, January 1991: (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Vendors Including Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Participant List/Agenda/Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
      - Directors' Meeting, January 1992: (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence with Vendors Including Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Budget Contracts (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Participant List/Agenda/Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Handouts from Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
      - Directors' Meeting, November 1992: (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence with Vendors Including Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Contracts/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Display Information from Resource Room (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Participant List/Agenda/Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Handouts at Meetings (Advisors & RIGs) (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
      - February 1993: (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence (Vendors & Participants) (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Agenda/Meeting Notes, Participation List (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Loose: Getty Folder (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
      - October 1993: (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
        - Participant List/Agenda/Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-66)
      - Directors/Funders Meeting, May 1994: (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Correspondence with Vendors (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Meeting Notes/Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Directors/Funders Meeting, January 1995: (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Correspondence with Participants (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Meeting Notes / Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Speeches (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Professional Development Directors Meeting – April 1995: (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
        - Participation List / Agenda / Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Directors Meeting, loose material, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
    - General correspondence and administration
      - Administration Memos 1987-88 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Administration Memos 1988-89 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Administration Memos 1990-91 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Administration Memos 1992-93 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Administration Memos 1994-95 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1992 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1993 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-67)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Correspondence with Directors for 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Budget Information (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Grant Guidelines (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Grant Tracking Log (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Documentation (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - List of Participating School Districts (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Regional Institute Grantee Meeting, April 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Regional Institute Database 1991/92 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Internal Memos for 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Internal Memos for 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - [Loose memos and correspondence,], 1994-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
      - Regional Institute Grants:
        - Loose papers regarding RIG Recommendations (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
        - Sacramento Regional Foundation: David F. Hess, Special Initiative Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
        - Loose papers regarding RIG Recommendations (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
        - Regional Institute Grants Faculty Program (Box 2007.IA.16-68)
        - Loose papers: Most of the box is filled with papers regarding Regional Institute Grants programs, recommendations, budgets, etc... 1993-1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - [Loose papers regarding Regional Institute Grant Program] (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
    - Student Assessment Grants:
      - Guidelines (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Review 1990, Internal Memos/Correspondence with Directors (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Review 1990, Correspondence with Reviewers, Panel Meeting, Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Review 1991, Internal Memos/Correspondence with Directors (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Review 1992, Internal Memos/Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Assessment Meeting, November 1989: (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - Correspondence with Participants and Speakers (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - List of Attendees (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - Meeting Notes/Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - [Loose Participant Packet with list of contents] (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
        - Collateral Materials (Speakers) (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Student Assessment Meeting, October 1990, Los Angeles (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
    - Regional Institute Technical Assistance Project:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Budget, September 13, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Project Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Contract with Ann Swartzberg (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Fundraising Information (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Regional Institute Video Project for Year 1993 (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
    - National Specialty Program Development Grants Administration:
      - Guidelines, June 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
      - Marketing (Box 2007.IA.16-69)
    - Interim/Progress Report/QE:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
      - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
      - Contracts (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
      - October 1993 (Box 2007.IA.16-70)
    - RIG Filemaker Pro database:
      - Budget, 1996-2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
      - Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
      - Internal memos, 1996-1999 (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
      - RAM Solutions contract/grant letters, 1996-1997 (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
      - Electronic records: Filemaker Pro databases of Regional Institute Grants, 1997-1999; undated; (7 Zip drives) (Box 2009.IA.38-03)
  - Transforming Education through the Arts Challenge (TETAC), Annenberg Challenge Grant
    - Annenberg Challenge Grant:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Final Proposal to Annenberg (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Contract with Michael Garber (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Letter of Inquiry (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
    - National Arts Education Consortium (NAEC):
      - Internal Memos, 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Program Manager, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Correspondence with Steering Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Correspondence with Annenberg, 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Communications Task Force, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
      - Fiscal Year 1997:
        - APS Press Releases (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Shell Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Grant Letters (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - APS Application (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - APS Selections/Announcements (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Annenberg Challenge Request for Proposals (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - APS Characteristics Chart (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Program Manager Interviews (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Steering Committee Meeting, Sept 28-30, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Steering Committee Meeting, May 13-14, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Laguna Meeting Notes, April 11-13, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Conference Calls (Box 2007.IA.16-71)
        - Progress Report, October 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
        - Finance/Fundraising Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
        - Program Task Force/Professional Development (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
        - Curriculum Task Force [2 files] (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
      - Fiscal Year 1998:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-72)
        - Correspondence with Program Manager (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Annenberg Arts Challenge Project Manager (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Steering Committee Conference Call Minutes/Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Steering Committee Meeting 1/12/97, Los Angeles (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Steering Committee Meeting 3/20/98 (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Steering Committee Meeting 4/28/97 to 5/1/97, Laguna Beach (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Steering Committee Meeting 10/27/97 to 10/28/97, Chicago (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Curriculum Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Development Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Professional Development Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Non-Selected TETAC (Transforming Education through the Arts Challenge) Schools (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Partner Schools List (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Fiscal Year 1998 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Reporting Guidelines/Timelines (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Technology Audit (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Spring 1998 Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
      - Fiscal Year 1999:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Correspondence with Project Manager (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-73)
        - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Curriculum Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Development Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Professional Development Task Force (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Fall 1998 Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Spring 1999 Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Steering Committee Minutes (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Mentors Meeting, April 1999 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Fiscal Year 2000:
        - Summer 1999 Convocation, LA (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Budget, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Correspondence with program manager, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Grant letter, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Correspondence, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Miscellaneous, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Internal memos, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Partner School Contact List, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Fiscal Year 2000 proposal, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Reporting Guidelines, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Resumes: Killeen, Wheetley, etc., FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Steering Committee Minutes, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Fall 1999 reports, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Spring 2000 reports, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
      - Chattanooga-Hamilton County Public Education Fund (NAEC), [original grant award letters], 1993-1994 (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
    - Evaluation:
      - Evaluation Search:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence for years 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence for year 1998 (NAEC, Task Force, GEI, Candidates) (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Assessment Meetings (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Agreements with Reviewers, Etc. (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Assess/Evaluation Task Force, Meeting Minutes (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Proposed Plan, Assess/Evaluation Design (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Evaluation Resource Document: UCLA/Westat (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Synthesis of Reviewer's Responses to Westat's Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
      - TETAC Evaluation, 1998 (Westat):
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence with NAEC (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Contracts with Reviewers & Westat (phase I & II) (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Phase I & II Proposal (April 1998 to June 1999) (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence with Reviewers (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - DBAE Expert Selection (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - School Instruments (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Westat Interviews / Conference Calls (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Westat's Monthly Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Meeting, March 14-16, 1998: (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
          - Miscellaneous/Participant List/Breakout (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
          - Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
          - Participant Packet (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Fiscal Year 1999 (Westat):
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - Phase II & III Proposal (7/99 to 6/00) (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - March-August 1998 Annual Report (Box 2007.IA.16-59)
        - [Loose 1st Semi-Annual Progress Report and other papers] (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Assessment/Evaluation Review Board Meeting (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Monthly Progress Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - 9/98 to 2/99 Mid-Year Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Spring 1998 Site Visits/Matrix (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Conference Presentation Proposals (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
      - Fiscal Year 2000 (Westat):
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Correspondence [2 files] (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - 1999 Review Board Meeting (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Monthly Progress Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - March-August 1999 Annual Report (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - 9/99 to 2/00 Mid-Year Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-60)
      - TETAC Evaluation (Westat), FY 2001
        - Budget, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Correspondence, FY 2001; (2 folders) (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Internal memos, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - "March-August '00 Annual Report" [Semi-annual report], October 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Mid-Year Progress Report, September 2000-February 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Mid-Year Progress Reports, Winter 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Monthly Progress Reports, 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Phase II and III contracts, FY 2000-2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Review Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
      - TETAC reports, reviews, and manuals:
        - Executive reports and progress reports, 1998-2000; undated (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - TETAC Year-End Progress Report, Summer 1999 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - TETAC Year-End Progress Report, Summer 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Final Evaluation Report of TETAC, July 2002 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Final Evaluation Report of the TETAC, Executive Summary, July 2002 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - TETAC Information Manual, 2000-2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - TETAC Information packet, November 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - Annenberg CPB, 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-02)
        - TETAC curriculum unit reviews, 1999-2000; (2 folders) (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
    - Marketing:
      - Fiscal Year 1994-1997:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - RIG Prof Dvpt Brochures/Ads 1994-96 (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - RIG NSP Marketing Reports (Spring 1995) (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Fiscal Year 1998:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Letters of Agreement (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - RIG Professional Development Brochures 1997-98 (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Spring 1998 Media Survey (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - JPGT Press Releases (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - National Press Coverage (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Media Aids for Partner Schools (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Fiscal Year 1999:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - RIG Professional Development Brochure 1999 (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - National Press Coverage (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Media Aids for Partner Schools (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Fiscal Year 2000:, 1999-2000
        - Budget (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Correspondence (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Internal memos (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - National press coverage (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Professional development brochure (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
    - Photo Doc, Fiscal Years 1998-99:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Contracts with Photographers (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Vicki's Speech Slides (includes photo) (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Correspondence/Slides by Claire Morales, 1992-97 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
      - Slide binders:
        - Texas RIG-TETAC Ladership Academy, June 25, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
        - Southeast Center for Education in the Arts, Renewal Institute, June 22-28, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
        - Ohio RIG-TETAC Leadership Academy, May 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
        - Nebraska RIG-TETAC Leadership Academy, September 17-18, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
        - TETAC Administrators meeting, Hazel Lucas' Class, May 8, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-58)
    - Documentation Project, Fiscal Year 2000:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-57)
- Special Initiative grants, 1986-1998; III.; 9.5 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
  The Special Initiative Grants program was a modestly funded program started in 1985 to support a variety of one-time projects that enhanced its efforts to improve the quality and status of art education in the schools. The GEI used the grants to encourage other organizations not participating directly in its operating projects to adopt and adapt a DBAE approach to arts education. The funds supported projects in the areas of publications, conferences, advocacy, assessment, and professional meetings.
  The records have been divided into several sections, which include one for special initiative grant recipients, two for Goals 2000 Art Education Leadership Fund and Educational Research and Improvement (ERIC), and one for special initiative grants administration. The Special Initiative grant recipients are in alphabetical order. The ERIC and Goals 2000 files are organized roughly chronologically. These two projects seem to be more closely associated with the other special initiative grants than with any other grant category and have, therefore, been described here. The administration section is loosely organized and only contains a few files.
  Records cover the implementation and general administration of the Special Initiative Grant program managed by the Getty Education Institute for the Arts (GEI) from 1986 to 1998. Each of the recipients is represented in the grant files, though in some cases only a copy of the grant award letter is present. Vicki Rosenberg is the Getty staff member who figures most prominently in the files. Types of documents found in the records include correspondence, memoranda, notes, proposals, reviews and evaluations, reports, and contracts that range in date from 1986 to 1998.
  - Special Initiative Grant Recipients
    - Alaska Art Education Association:
      - Grant Offer Letter, June 26, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Alaska Arts in Education, Inc: Jan Lovett original grant letter (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
    - American Council for the Arts:
      - Original grant letter (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
    - Arizona State University:
      - "HRC Mary Erickson grant," [original grant award letters], 1999 (Box 2009.IA.38-02)
      - Hispanic Research Center: Phase II – Unfunded, 1997-98 (Box 2007.IA.16-80)
      - Hispanic Research Center (ASU) (Box 2007.IA.16-80)
    - California Art Education Association:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - California Art Education Association, February-March 1988 (closed) (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
    - California Arts Council:, 1994
      - Original grant award letters (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
    - California State University at Los Angeles, June 1992 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
    - Consortium of Black Organizations for the Arts:
      - Grant Offer Letter, April 29, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Consortium of Black Organizations for the Arts Inc/Eugene Grigsby original grant letter (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
    - Council for Basic Education:
      - Grant Offer Letter, July 3, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
      - Council for Basic Education original grant letter (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers (CCSSO):
      - 1989-1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Grant Offer Letter, August 25, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-74)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Education Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Grant Offer Letter, June 13, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Final Report, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Internal Memos, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Proposal/Budget, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - National Council of State Art Education Consultants (NCSAEC) and CCSSO: (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Budget, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Final Report, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Grant Letter, April 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Internal Memos, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
        - Proposal, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Assessment Schedule (loose) (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Quarterly Report 1995/96 (loose) (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Year-End Report 1994-1995 (loose) (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - (unlabeled folder) (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - National Assessment of Education Progress Project (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Notes on AEAC Meetings/Presentations (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Quarterly Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-75)
      - Council of Chief State School Officers / Gordon Ambach [original grant award letters], 1991-1997 (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
    - Education Writers Association: